highstakeholdings.com 2010-05-22

# High Stake Holdings

**Privacy Policy**

To the extent that your sensitive personal data is processed, we will employ appropriate security measures given the nature of that data. However, you recognise that your use of the Internet and our website is entirely at your own risk. We have done the best to create a secure and reliable website for our users. However, we have no responsibility or liability for the security of personal information transmitted via the Internet. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Highstakeholdings.com uses forms in which you give us contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can request information and support, and make suggestions if any. 

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way, including through email or other communications with our customer service department. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given and the transcript of your communication. 

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system. 

We use cookies to identify you so you don't need to login each time you visit our site. They are linked to your 'Username' which is associated with the information in your account. 

This site also contains links to other websites. Unfortunately, Highstakeholdings.com does not take responsibility of the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Data backups are taken every 8 hours in order to maintain a backup copy of the entire member database to prevent data loss, just incase we experience hardware failures. 

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

We cooperate with Government and Law Enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties in case we, in our sole discretion, believe is necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity that we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

**What Happens to my Personal Information if I cancel my account?**

When your Highstakeholdings.com account is canceled (either voluntarily or involuntarily), all of your personally identifiable information is placed on "deactivated" status on our relevant databases. However, you should know that the deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information, if necessary, in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements. 

**Changes in Our Practices**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes to our Privacy Statement, our Home Page, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our Home Page, at least 30 days prior to the implementation of the changes. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this Highstakeholdings.com, or your dealings with Highstakeholdings.com, please contact support.
